welcome to my talk I'm on VLC Avis I
欢迎来到我在VLC Avis上的演讲
work for a consultancy company in
在一家咨询公司工作
Belgium called Dina and I've been
比利时叫Dina，我去过
completely contributing to a new library
完全为新图书馆做贡献
well it's about a year old or a year and
好吧，大约一岁或一年，
a half
一半
called spring res Docs so my title is
叫做spring res Docs，所以我的标题是
writing comprehensive and guaranteed
写作全面有保证
up-to-date rest API documentation that's
最新的REST API文档
quite a handful but I actually want to
少数几个，但我实际上想
make it a bit longer I wanted to write
让它更长一点，我想写
writing comprehensive and guaranteed
写作全面有保证
up-to-date REST API documentation using
使用的最新REST API文档
a test driven approach that's actually
实际上是一种测试驱动的方法
quite unique and it really gives you
非常独特，它真的给你
some nice benefits when writing
写作时有一些不错的好处
documentation and I'll try to explain
文档，我将尽力解释
why in the next couple of slides so when
为什么在接下来的几张幻灯片中，当
we're actually setting out to select the
我们实际上是开始选择
tool to write documentation we must
编写文档的工具，我们必须
really think about some of the concepts
真正考虑一些概念
and principles that really help us write
真正帮助我们写作的原则
good documentation which is constantly
良好的文档，不断
up to date so the most important thing
最新，所以最重要的是
in writing documentation is that it's
在书面文件中是
accurate because I would argue that
准确，因为我认为
having no documentation at all is better
完全没有文档会更好
than having an accurate documentation
比拥有准确的文档
people are going to be frustrated
人们会感到沮丧
they're gonna lose our time they're
他们会浪费我们的时间
going to and if they feel like when they
去，如果他们感觉像当他们
reach our documentation they can't trust
获得他们无法信任的文档
it so then basically they're going to
所以基本上他们要
ignore it and then you just have a bunch
忽略它，然后你只有一堆
of documentation which you can't really
您无法真正了解的文档
do anything with so you have to have
做任何事情，所以你必须
some means in the tool lets you select
该工具中的某些方法可让您选择
that guarantees us that our
保证我们
documentation will be up to date and
文档将是最新的，并且
using a test driven approach I think we
我认为使用测试驱动的方法
can achieve this because your tests will
可以实现这一目标，因为您的测试将
actually fail in case your documentation
真的失败了，以防您的文档
is not up to date anymore so I'll show
已经不最新了，我将显示
how that works in just a bit so then
它如何工作，然后
also an important thing to get right
正确也是一件重要的事情
with the tool that you chooses the
使用您选择的工具
documents in the right place it might be
文档可能在正确的位置
a bit abstract so basically when you're
有点抽象，所以基本上当你
when you have a traditional spring MVC
当您拥有传统的春季MVC时
flow you basically have a domain model a
流，你基本上有一个领域模型
POJO which then is treated by controller
POJO然后由控制器处理
controller method basically has a
控制器方法基本上有一个
request mapping and takes the pocho and
请求映射并接受pocho和
then
然后
translates it into Jason eventually but
最终将其翻译成杰森，但
how that how that actually works is it's
实际运作方式是
using a response entity everybody is
使用响应实体，每个人都是
familiar with with spring MVC yeah right
熟悉Spring MVC是的
and then there are some Jackson going on
然后有一些杰克逊继续
if you use Jason
如果您使用杰森
so that's doing some custom stuff for
所以这是做一些自定义的东西
instance as some serialize ur some
实例化一些序列化您的一些
custom serializers it looks at some
自定义序列化程序，它看起来有些
annotations on your your domain model
您的域模型上的注释
and then eventually you've got the HTTP
然后最终您有了HTTP
response okay so if you use a tool like
可以，所以如果您使用类似
swagger
昂首阔步
it actually looks at your controller and
它实际上看着您的控制器，
add some annotations there and it tries
在其中添加一些注释，然后尝试
to deduct information by doing static
通过静态扣除信息
analysis of your code but basically what
分析您的代码，但基本上是什么
the flaw in that system is that it's
该系统的缺点是
actually in the wrong place because you
实际上在错误的地方，因为你
should really be documenting the HTTP
应该真的在记录HTTP
response because swagger how can I
反应，因为我会大张旗鼓
actually figure out what Jackson is
弄清楚杰克逊是什么
doing it's by kind of trying to deduct
这样做是通过尝试扣除
that but it will eventually always fail
但这最终将永远失败
I mean in some of the cases that go fail
我的意思是在某些情况下失败了
so it will be better that we have a tool
所以最好有一个工具
that looks at your HTTP response and
查看您的HTTP响应，
your HP request which actually is a
您的HP请求实际上是
place where where you can be guaranteed
可以保证的地方
that that's what your client is going to
那就是你的客户要
receive and what the client is going to
接收和客户端将要做什么
send so that should be the place okay
发送，所以应该是可以的地方
and spring Red Sox is actually looking
春天的红袜实际上正在寻找
at that point okay so that's the
在那个时候好吧，那是
difference you got to keep it dry so
你必须保持干燥的差异，所以
your your controller has to the
您的控制器必须
contradict yourself in the controller
在控制器中与自己矛盾
because if you do then you're going to
因为如果这样做，那么您将
get out of sync and your documentation
失去同步，您的文档
not gonna be up to date anymore
不会再更新了
so here you have a a create and
所以在这里你有一个创造和
eventually a an exception Handler and
最终是一个异常处理程序，
the Creator is going to return a
创造者将要返回
response status created so if you just
已创建响应状态，因此，如果您只是
look at the two drinks of it the create
看看它创造的两种饮料
method what you do in send it to like
方法您将其发送给喜欢的方法
swagger is to annotate this with some
招摇是用一些注释
documentation annotations so here we
文档注释，所以在这里我们
actually mentioning that the response
实际提到回应
can be 400 or 201 so as you can see you
可以是400或201，这样就可以看到
have the application here and if you
在这里有应用程序，如果您
change your bad request or create it to
更改您的错误请求或将其创建为
something else then you have to remember
还有其他事情，你必须记住
to update
更新
the annotation so that's something that
注释，这就是
could get out of sync quickly pretty
可能很快就会变得不同步
quickly so it's also some flaw there and
很快，所以那里也有一些缺陷，
actually when we are writing
实际上当我们在写作时
documentation it's a my opinion not
文档不是我的意见
sufficient to just have things
足以拥有东西
generators you also want to write some
发电机，你也想写一些
stuff which is functional some real text
某些真实文本起作用的东西
that helps the client the consumer of
帮助客户的消费者
your service to to basically understand
您的服务要基本了解
the service better so when you're doing
服务更好，所以当你做的时候
that it's it's a good idea to write that
写那是一个好主意
in in a tool that's that's actually
在一个实际上是
designed for writing documentation and
设计用于编写文档和
markdown or asciidoc I think we all know
markdown或asciidoc我想我们都知道
that either one of the two it's a great
两者中的任何一个都很棒
way of writing documentation plain text
编写文档纯文本的方式
or maybe more sophisticated syntax like
或者更复杂的语法，例如
tables and stuff that's actually a
桌子和东西实际上是
really easy way to do that and if you
真的很简单，如果
want to do that with something else
想用别的东西做
which doesn't which is not really
这不是，不是真的
designed for that you're gonna have a
为您设计的
hard time okay so these are important
很难，所以这些很重要
things to get right and spring grass
正确的事情和春天的草
talks uses the test driven approach to
会谈使用测试驱动方法
achieve these things so let's take a
实现这些事情，所以让我们来
look at how that actually works so first
首先看看它是如何工作的
basically write integration tests which
基本上写集成测试
constantly execute in these integration
在这些整合中不断执行
tests you can add a hook and you can
测试您可以添加一个钩子，您可以
find that when it actually does the
发现它实际执行时
request and response but it uses that
请求和响应，但它使用
information that it that it got from
从中获得的信息
that to document that stuff I'll get
来证明我会得到的东西
into that later as well so once you've
以后也一样，一旦
got is these integration tests it can
这些集成测试可以
generate information snippets based on
根据以下信息生成信息摘要
whatever III retrieved from from running
从运行中获取的任何III
the tests these snippets can then be
然后可以测试这些片段
used in a asciidoc or a markdown file
在asciidoc或markdown文件中使用
where you include that so that's really
你在其中包括那是真的
simple then you actually write in the in
简单，然后您实际上就在
the template you write the stuff that
您编写的模板
it's not gonna change going to change
改变不会改变
but that's giving me more insights in
但这给了我更多的见解
the API and the stuff that's often
API和通常的东西
changing is automatically generated from
变化是自动产生的
the tests so that's a nice combo and
测试，所以这是一个很好的组合，
then eventually you compile that into an
然后最终您将其编译为
HTML we're also doing in PDF or whatever
我们也在PDF或其他格式中使用HTML
which is going to be your eventual
这最终将是你
documentation so that's the way rest
文档，这就是休息的方式
Doc's works
Doc的作品
and it's really a test driven approach
这实际上是一种测试驱动的方法
so let's look at our each of the
让我们来看看我们每个
individuals stages how that actually
个人分阶段如何
would look like in the code so if here
看起来像在代码中，所以如果在这里
got a traditional mo can we see call is
有一个传统的莫，我们可以看到电话是
everybody familiar with mo can we see
每个熟悉莫的人都能看到
can I show induce your hands all right
我可以展示一下让你的手好吗
yeah that's just about everyone so yeah
是的，几乎每个人都这样
so basically this is pretty
所以基本上这很漂亮
straightforward you just do a get on on
很简单，你只是继续
you try to get the first car here and
你尝试在这里买第一辆车，
then going to do assert that which is
然后去断言那是
this is always the stuff you're going to
这总是你要去的东西
be doing in your integration test you
在进行集成测试时
just check if the state is okay and then
只是检查状态是否正常，然后
what's res Doc's doing is actually
Doc在做什么，实际上是
tuning the aunts do methods of mocking
调姑妈做嘲笑的方法
Lacey to add a hook to generate some
莱西添加一个钩子来生成一些
documentation and with that you can
文档，您可以
actually start providing some
实际上开始提供一些
documentation with the descriptions of
说明文件
for instance the parameter with the name
例如带有名称的参数
car ID or response fields so for
汽车ID或响应字段，因此
instance you get back response field
实例您返回响应字段
brands you can here actually on this in
您可以在这里实际使用的品牌
this place you can describe it and not
这个地方你可以描述它而不是
in the production code where you would
在生产代码中
use an annotation you would have code
使用您将有代码的注释
blood so there's also a possibility to
血液，所以也有可能
reuse documentation of common fields
重用常见字段的文档
that always come back in every request
总是在每个请求中回来
and response and that's much more by the
和回应，而更多的是
way which I'll get into later so this
我稍后会介绍的方式
this is what you got in your integration
这就是整合中得到的
test then this generates the snippets
测试然后生成片段
the so these things in this case it's
所以在这种情况下，这些东西是
asciidoc can be mocked down as well you
asciidoc也可以被嘲笑
get a crawl request which you can then
收到一个抓取请求，然后您就可以
display in your documentation so people
显示在您的文档中，以便人们
can test it you can also use HTTP I
可以测试它，也可以使用HTTP I
which is more sophisticated curl
卷曲更复杂
basically as also some coloring in the
基本上也有一些着色
response and requests bodies and that
回应和要求机构，以及
this is new and one with one by I by the
这是新的，我一一与
way and also just the traditional HTTP
方式，也只有传统的HTTP
request annotation so you got requests
请求注释，以便您收到请求
snippets you can also do the request
您也可以执行请求的代码段
both parameter snippets which will
两个参数片段
document a table automatically generated
记录自动生成的表
with the parameter name and the
参数名称和
description which is then the dot of
说明，然后是
course from what you entered in your
您输入的课程
test then response snippets
然后测试响应片段
will also be the similar thing as the
也将与
requests snippets where you can see the
请求片段，您可以在其中查看
response body if there's if there's
响应主体是否存在
and you can do the same for request body
您可以对请求正文进行相同的操作
and I mean there's a whole bunch of
我的意思是有一堆
snippets that are automatically
自动摘录
generated so here you can see the ones
生成的，所以在这里您可以看到
we already talked about request girl
我们已经讨论过请求女孩
HTTP HTTP by request fields because both
HTTP HTTP by request字段，因为两者
by remiel parameters and request timers
通过remiel参数和请求计时器
parameters sorry the headers as well can
参数也很遗憾标题
also be generated and request parts if
也可以生成并请求零件
you got a multi-part request it also is
您有一个多部分的请求，它也是
possible to generate documentation for
可能为生成文档
that on the response side you've got
在回应方面，你有
response fields hyper media links
响应字段超媒体链接
response headers and response fields I
响应标头和响应字段I
mean I just want to get a little bit
意思是我只想得到一点
into the hypermedia links it's run using
进入它正在使用的超媒体链接
hyper media or knows about hyper media
超媒体或了解超媒体
okay so not that many hyper media
好，所以没有那么多超媒体
basically allows you to link from one
基本上可以让您从一个链接
resource to another so that you don't
资源给另一个，这样你就不会
have to bookmark all the the your eyes
必须标记所有的眼睛
of all the resources so that's the
所有资源中，所以
decoupling and it's it's actually pretty
去耦，实际上很漂亮
difficult to document that because you
很难记录下来，因为你
really have to look into the response
真的必须调查响应
body where there's a link in the Jason
Jason中有链接的身体
for instance which then provides you a
例如，然后为您提供
to your I of the other resource and if
给你我的其他资源，如果
you are taking a Eurocentric approach to
您正在采取以欧洲为中心的方法
your documentation if you're for
您的文档，如果您要
instance like what swagger does take you
像招摇摇晃地带你的例子
display a whole list of your eyes that
显示您的整个眼睛列表
you have available in your API people
您的API人员有空
are going to bookmark that and that's
将添加书签，那就是
what you want to avoid with using hyper
您想要避免使用hyper
media so in this approach you basically
媒体，因此您基本上可以通过这种方式
get hyper media links as a table in your
在您的表格中获取超媒体链接
documentation I'll also show that in a
文档中，我还将在
demo later on and so this allows you to
稍后进行演示，因此您可以
decouple much and enforce decoupling as
解耦很多，并强制解耦为
well so that's supported out-of-the-box
好，所以开箱即用
okay so those are the snippets and then
好吧，这些是片段，然后
let's take a look at the documentation
让我们看一下文档
templates that you'd have to write in a
您必须在其中编写的模板
ski talk or in markdown so you can see
滑雪谈话或降价促销，这样您就可以看到
it's it's pretty easy to write this you
这很容易写给你
wouldn't want to write stuff in there
不想在那里写东西
that's going to change a lot just some
这将改变很多，只是一些
some functional information to help the
一些功能信息，以帮助
client developer to understand it better
客户开发人员更好地了解它
and then you basically include the the
然后您基本上将
snippets there so you can see path bar
在那里的片段，您可以看到路径栏
mears parameters and curl requests
磨损参数和卷曲请求
it's being included like that so pretty
像那样被包括在内
straightforward right okay so once you
直截了当好吧，所以一旦你
got the template you got the snippets
得到了模板，得到了摘录
you can generate the HTML and that looks
您可以生成HTML，看起来
pretty neat it just basically formats
基本上整齐，基本上是格式
everything for you and it includes the
为您准备的一切，包括
snippets that you've generated okay so
您生成的片段好吗
that's basically the most important part
这基本上是最重要的部分
of rest Doc's how that works okay so let
其余Doc的工作原理还不错，所以让
me show a quick demo then okay so have
我演示一个快速演示然后好吧
it's not visible if you have to clone
如果必须克隆则看不到
that
那
all right
好吧
yeah all right oh wait wrong screen okay
是的，好的，哦，等待错误的屏幕，好吗
this one all right so we've have
这个好吧，所以我们有
basically a very simple application here
基本上是一个非常简单的应用程序
and extremely simple it's probably the
而且非常简单，可能是
most simple demo you're ever going to
您将要进行的最简单的演示
see in this in this conference so we
在这次会议上看到这一点，所以我们
have a car controller we've got a car
有汽车管理员，我们有汽车
and a driver so the car basically it has
和司机，所以汽车基本上是
an ID a brand and doors and then you've
一个ID，一个品牌和门，然后
got a car controller that basically
有了一个汽车控制器，基本上
takes it returns the car as an API it
把它作为API返回汽车
uses your I cars slash ID and so that's
使用您的I汽车斜线ID，因此
really simple it doesn't really use a
非常简单，实际上并没有使用
back-end or whatever I'm just returning
后端或我刚刚返回的任何内容
it statically but okay it basically is
它是静态的，但是好吧，基本上是
there to demonstrate what tests driven
在那里展示什么测试驱动
approach would look like so the car
方法看起来像这样的车
controller basically returns the car so
控制器基本上是回车的
I have a demo application here wait a
我有一个演示应用程序在这里等待
test here sorry and it tests okay so
在这里测试不好意思，所以可以测试
this basically does what I've been
这基本上就是我去过的
showing in the slides so you've got the
在幻灯片中显示，这样您就可以
mock MVC call here which does the
在这里模拟MVC调用
perform just catch the car and it does
表演只是赶车，它确实
the N expect which is sorts ok so that's
N期望这是可以的，所以
pretty straightforward and then we've
非常简单，然后我们已经
got the end do which can document the
完成了可以记录
car and the get part of the resource we
汽车和获取资源的一部分
do a pre process response there that's
在那里进行预处理响应
basically when it's when it does the
基本上是什么时候
request already response in mock embassy
要求已在模拟使馆内回复
before you put it into a snippet you can
在将其放入片段之前，您可以
actually do some stuff with that in this
实际上在这方面做了一些事情
case be pretty printed so that it looks
外壳要漂亮地印刷，以便看起来
nice in the documentation you can do a
在文档中不错，您可以
lot of stuff there anything you're
很多东西，你在做什么
thinking about you can think about and
想着你可以想一想
then we've got links so with the links
那么我们有链接，所以链接
thing that's a hypermedia part we can
这是我们可以做的超媒体部分
actually say that ok when you have that
其实说好吧
car resource you get back a driver
您找回司机的汽车资源
resource as a link as well because every
资源也是一个链接，因为每个
car will have a driver ok and then you
汽车将有一个好的司机，然后你
can document that link what it actually
可以记录该链接的实际内容
does I mean this is pretty
我的意思是这很漂亮
straightforward simple stuff but you can
简单明了的东西，但是你可以
get really sophisticated in this and
在这方面变得非常复杂
then the path parameter so the car
然后是路径参数
I D and the response fields okay so
ID和响应字段可以
that's straightforward let's run this
很简单，让我们运行这个
okay so let's do it may even can do it
好吧，让我们去做，甚至可以做到
as well which a unit is matter okay so
以及哪个单位还可以
success that's fine and what it actually
成功是好的，实际上是什么
does in the target here it gives you a
确实在这里的目标，它给你一个
tremendous it gives you generated
它给您带来巨大的收益
snippets so in that folder that you
片段，以便您在该文件夹中
mentioned here you will get a couple of
在这里提到你会得到一些
these a doc files which already snippets
这些已经摘要的doc文件
so if we look at those snippets it's
因此，如果我们看一下这些片段，
just one we're in slides right so the
只是我们在幻灯片中，所以
curl and then with the links you get a
卷曲，然后通过链接获得
table just like with the response fields
就像响应字段一样
or request fields HD by all the stuff is
或要求所有内容的高清字段是
there okay so you've got these snippets
好的，所以您有这些摘要
now you want to generate this into an
现在您想将其生成为
HTML so that we can actually expose this
HTML，以便我们实际上可以公开
as documentation so what you can do
作为文档，所以您可以做什么
there is you have to write in API guides
您必须在API指南中编写
or some ASCII doc file or some markdown
或某些ASCII文档文件或某些减价
file like this so here you can see with
这样的文件，所以在这里您可以看到
asciidoc that you have a lot of stuff
你有很多东西
like the doctype which will then be a
就像doctype一样
book in this case but you can also make
在这种情况下预订，但您也可以
it a PDF or any other back-end from
它是PDF还是其他任何后端
ASCII doc howdy : you can also do
ASCII doc howdy：您也可以
highlighting which is pretty neat so if
突出显示这很整洁，所以如果
you have Jason it will be nicely
你有杰森，那就很好
highlighted in the in the eventual
最终在中突出显示
documentation you can also do a table of
文档，你也可以做一个表
contents so that's for free you don't
内容，所以这是免费的，您不会
have to write that yourself asciidoc
必须写你自己asciidoc
supplies this it lets the clients a
提供这个让客户
developer basically navigate much easier
开发人员基本上可以轻松导航
through your big documentation and then
通过您的大型文档，然后
you've got a lot of stuff you can you
你有很多东西可以
can mention which is probably not gonna
可以提到哪个可能不会
change a lot just some easy to write
改变很多，只是一些易于编写
documentation and then you get on to the
文档，然后进入
actual resources where we have these
我们拥有这些的实际资源
inclusions okay so these are the
内含物好，所以这些是
snippets that we just saw in the folder
我们刚刚在文件夹中看到的片段
and the target folder and how they're
以及目标文件夹及其状态
actually being generated because I ran
实际上是因为我跑了而产生的
the test the the maven install I have
测试我的Maven安装
the documentation
文档
in the generated dogs right so here you
在生成的狗中，所以在这里你
just have the HTML if I open that I can
只要打开HTML就可以了
show it in okay so this is basically
可以显示出来，所以基本上
where I can generate it so it looks
在哪里可以生成它，看起来
pretty good and it's super easy you just
很好，你很容易
these these are the these little
这些这些都是这些
snippets and you can do whatever what
片段，您可以做什么
you want with them in your asciidoc file
您希望与他们一起在asciidoc文件中
or your markdown file okay so basically
或您的markdown文件好了，基本上
that's what you want to get and your
那就是你想要得到的，而你的
test makes that really easy so let me
测试真的很容易，所以让我
show you how how it guarantees that it's
向您展示如何保证它的
up to date so in this case we have in
是最新的，因此在这种情况下
our tests although let's go to our
我们的测试，尽管让我们去
production code in the core controller
核心控制器中的生产代码
you see that we have doors for instance
你看到我们有门
so in the car we have doors let's say I
所以在车上我们有门，说我
refactor the code and I remove doors so
重构代码，我移开了门
the doors are no longer supported so
门不再受支持，所以
it's easy so what would happen of course
这很容易，所以当然会发生什么
here go to a break and now actually my
这里休息一下，现在实际上是我的
documentation it's not longer no longer
文档不再不再
up to date it's not in sync with the
到目前为止，它与
production code because it's going to
生产代码，因为它将
document that there is going to be a
文档将有一个
divorce fields and a response and the
离婚领域和回应以及
clients might actually count on that so
客户实际上可能会指望如此
that's an issue right you want to make
这是您要提出的问题
sure that now if we try to deploy this
确保现在，如果我们尝试部署此
if you try to build this even that it's
如果您尝试构建它，即使它是
going to fail so if I do that
将会失败，所以如果我那样做
no it's failing so here it's basically
不，它失败了，所以这里基本上
saying that there are testing errors and
说有测试错误，
snippet fields with the following in
包含以下内容的摘要字段
this case it's not really shown well
这种情况下并没有很好地显示
here yeah so snippet exception feels
是的，所以片段摘要的感觉
with a following path or not found in
具有以下路径或在以下位置找不到
the payload doors so we're messing doors
负载门，所以我们把门弄糟了
in in the payload so the documentation
在有效负载中，因此文档
is there but but the payload isn't
有，但有效载荷不存在
showing it so that's that's an out of
显示它，所以那是出于
data issue so basically what solution
数据问题基本上有什么解决办法
would be is to just change the test you
就是改变你的测试
can do that in the other way around as
可以以另一种方式做到这一点
well of course mmm and here we just
好吧，嗯，在这里，我们只是
remove the description for doors and
删除门的描述和
then of course if we're going to write
那当然如果我们要写
it it's going to work again and then we
它会再次工作，然后我们
can just look at our documentation again
可以再看看我们的文档
okay so almost done okay working yeah
好的，所以差不多完成了，可以工作
let's check this out again and here you
让我们再次检查一下，在这里你
can see that now there's no more doors
可以看到现在没有门了
in response structure okay so that's the
在响应结构中，所以这是
guaranteed up-to-date
保证最新
nature of spring rest Docs okay so I
春天休息的性质Docs好吗，所以我
talked about how spring res Docs works
谈到了spring res Docs的工作方式
now let's see a bit of the other
现在让我们看看其他
features that spring grass Docs can
Spring Docs可以提供的功能
offer so we've seen that you have this
提供，所以我们已经看到您有这个
HTML generated and it's really easy to
生成了HTML，并且非常容易
package that within your application of
在您的应用程序中打包
course it's in your target folder
当然在目标文件夹中
already but you can put it any source
已经，但是你可以放任何来源
main resources a few spring boot would
主要资源有一些春季靴子
be automatically available as well for
也可以自动用于
your consumer in the same application on
您的消费者在同一应用程序上
the same port and host so that's really
相同的端口和主机，所以实际上
simple it's also easy to customize the
简单，也很容易自定义
request a response before it's
要求回复之前
documented we've seen that with this
记录下来，我们已经看到了这一点
pretty prints pre-processing
漂亮的照片预处理
you can do anything every so that's
你可以做任何事情，所以
really simple to do there's also support
真的很简单，也有支持
for reusing the common documentation so
重用通用文档
we've seen in one of the slides that you
我们在其中一张幻灯片中看到
can have some fields that are always
可以有一些总是
recurring in every in every call that
在每个呼叫中​​重复出现的每个呼叫
you're doing and everything that you
你正在做的一切
want to be your mana documents that's
想要成为你的魔法文件
easy to also reuse so you don't have to
易于重用，因此您不必
repeat yourself endlessly
无休止地重复自己
then you can also add extra information
然后您还可以添加其他信息
to the snippets so the snippets are by
到片段，因此片段是
default generated but you can you can
默认生成，但可以
change that you can change the way
改变你可以改变方式
they're generated you can add extra
它们是生成的，您可以添加额外的
extra columns to these tables for
这些表的额外列
instance if you want to document the
实例，如果您想记录
constraints which I'll get to later you
我以后会遇到的限制
can just add a column and then add some
可以只添加一列，然后添加一些
extra fields or action let's add some
额外的字段或动作，让我们添加一些
extra information it's also done in the
额外的信息也可以在
fluent API that we saw in the
我们在
integration test so the constraints are
集成测试，因此约束是
easy to document in that approach but
用这种方法很容易记录下来，但是
you can also use a sort of introspection
你也可以使用内省
into annotations which could be on your
放入您的注释中
domain model which might say it nonno or
可能会说为nonno或
something like that or minimum or
诸如此类或最小值或
maximum although we've seen that with
最大，尽管我们已经看到了
that approach that you're reverting a
您要还原的方法
little bit to the swagger approach where
有点招摇的方法在哪里
you're trying to deduct information so
您正在尝试扣除信息，以便
be careful with that but obviously it's
对此要小心，但显然是
also possible to do that manually and
也可以手动进行
then you can also ignore parts of the
那么您也可以忽略部分
request or the response during the
请求或响应期间
documentation so when you're actually
文档，因此当您实际上
when you're getting a response back so
当您收到回复时，
the payload is returned to you then you
有效载荷返回给您，然后您
might not want to document everything so
可能不想记录所有内容，所以
you can ignore certain things that are
您可以忽略某些
being returned it turned to you because
被归还给你，因为
and you can also pre process that so you
您还可以进行预处理，以便您
can just make sure it's not even shown
可以确保它甚至没有显示
in the documentation and you can also
在文档中，您还可以
switch off failing all together so it
关闭所有一起失败，所以
lets say you have a payload of 100
假设您的有效载荷为100
fields right and you just want to
正确的字段，而您只想
document two fields then to make sure
然后记录两个字段以确保
that the documentation wouldn't fail on
该文档不会失败
fields that it discovers in the payload
它在有效载荷中发现的字段
and it didn't find in the in the
而且在中找不到
documentation you have to you basically
基本上需要的文件
have to ignore explicitly ninety-eight
必须明确地忽略九十八
fields in your integration test which
集成测试中的哪些字段
will be grandmas so you can just switch
将是奶奶，所以你可以切换
off the failing in case you have that
如果你有失败的话
specific scenario you can also mark
您还可以标记特定场景
parts of the requested responses
部分要求的回复
optional so that if you document them
可选的，以便您记录它们
and they're not always coming back
他们并不总是回来
because you have a lot of different
因为你有很多不同
cases you want to document then you can
您想要记录的案例，那么您可以
say okay this is optional I'm not going
说好吧，这是可选的，我不去
to fail in case this field is not
如果此字段不是
returned in a specific case okay so this
在特定情况下还可以，所以这
this is absolutely guarantee that your
这绝对保证您的
documentation is it's going to be in
文档将在
sync with your with your payload or your
与您的有效负载或您的同步
actual request and response you can't do
您无法做的实际要求和回应
that
那
so it's not absolute
所以这不是绝对的
then we have basically support for both
那么我们基本上都支持
Jason and XML so we've seen Jason
Jason和XML，所以我们已经看过Jason
examples but it's just as well works
例子，但是效果很好
with XML so that comes out of the box as
XML，因此可以直接使用
well and then now we have support for
好吧，现在我们对
rest assured that since the 1.1 so rest
放心，因为1.1所以休息
assured is basically an alternative for
放心基本上是
markup McCann BC but the big benefit
加价麦肯省，但受益匪浅
here is that you don't need to have
这是你不需要
spring to run spring rest Docs because
春天来运行春天休息文档，因为
you can use rest assured okay so it used
您可以放心使用，这样就可以了
to be coupled with maken BC so you
与maken BC相结合，所以您
needed to use maka need to use spring
需要使用马卡需要使用弹簧
MBC but with brass this shirt it's it's
MBC但用黄铜这件衬衫是
no longer needed is anyone using rest
不再需要休息的人
assured by the way okay so a couple all
放心，好吧，所以一对夫妇
right so you can now use spring Red Sox
对，所以您现在可以使用春季红袜
out-of-the-box and then something really
开箱即用
interesting is you can use these
有趣的是您可以使用这些
snippets for stubbing purposes you kind
您用于存根的摘要
of have these integration tests and they
有这些集成测试，他们
generate request and response
生成请求和响应
information and this stuff is basically
信息，这东西基本上是
a great candidate for stopping
停止的好人选
um but brownfields because you first
嗯，但棕地，因为你先
have to write your API and then test it
必须编写您的API然后进行测试
your integration test before it can
您的集成测试之前
actually start generating these snippets
实际上开始生成这些片段
so if you would want to have stubbing
所以如果你想存根
and for a greenfield project which
对于一个新建项目
doesn't really create it yet you
并没有真正创建它
wouldn't be able to use this approach
将无法使用这种方法
but it would be very nice to if you have
但是如果有的话
already an API to use this and then you
已经有一个API可以使用它，然后您
can take these snippets
可以拿这些片段
put them in for instance wire mock and
把它们放在例如电线模拟和
serve that to the consumers as well and
也为消费者服务
that's also going to be guaranteed up to
这也将得到保证
date okay so that's pretty neat right
日期还可以，所以很整洁吧
okay so basically that was a short
好吧，基本上这是一个简短的
introduction it's only 20 minutes 30
简介只有20分钟30
minutes so definitely check out the the
分钟，所以一定要看看
repo and I can say as a contributor that
回购，作为贡献者，我可以说
really if you contribute to this
真的，如果你对此有所贡献
repository it's it's really great to
仓库真的很棒
have Andy Wilkinson the project lead
让Andy Wilkinson担任项目负责人
review your code gave me some great
查看您的代码给了我一些很棒的东西
great insights so it's still still
很棒的见解，所以至今仍然
building
建造
but the stuff that's already there is
但是已经有东西了
super useful reusing a money of our
重用我们的钱非常有用
clients and they're all very happy with
客户，他们都非常满意
this so this is this is a nice
这是一个不错的选择
alternative to swagger so if you're
摇摇欲坠的替代方案，如果你是
looking for a tool especially for
寻找一个特别的工具
hypermedia purposes this is great but
超媒体的目的，这很好，但是
for any other IPI as well where you want
以及您需要的任何其他IPI
to have this guaranteed up to date
保证最新
without intruding your codes your
而不会干扰您的代码
production code with annotations then
然后带有注释的生产代码
definitely give Spring Red Sox a try
绝对可以尝试春季红袜
okay is there still time left yes
好吧，还有时间吗？
yeah I can show you that so for adding a
是的，我可以向您展示，以便添加
property I can quickly show that so for
属性，我可以快速证明这一点
instance you have your car what property
实例你有你的车什么财产
would you want to add windows ok all
你想添加所有的窗口吗
right so you got it the windows right ok
对，所以你就把窗户弄好了
and now of course I'll use it so it's
现在我当然会用它
basically just the other way around and
基本上只是相反
that works perfectly as well so how many
效果很好，有多少
windows six I don't know five ok so now
Windows六，我不知道五，所以现在
if I if I run this that should fail
如果我运行它，那应该失败
again right so in this approach it's
再次正确，所以在这种方法中
going to happen exactly like that it's
完全会像那样发生
going to fail because you're basically
会失败，因为你基本上是
missing fields in the documentation and
文档中缺少字段，并且
it's saying that as well
也是这样说
in a simple manner so the following
以简单的方式，所以以下
parts of the payload were not document
有效负载的一部分不是文档
and then you've got actually snippet of
然后您实际上得到了
the payload that you forgot so then you
你忘记的有效载荷，所以你
just have to add that in your
只需将其添加到您的
documentation and that you work very
文档，并且您工作得非常好
simple way as well
也是简单的方法
so Windows the amount of windows of this
所以Windows这个窗口的数量
car right and then we just run this
车正确，然后我们就运行这个
again now it won't fail you more I hope
现在再次希望它不会让你失望
pretty confident okay
很有信心
and now if I still have Chrome open
现在，如果我仍然打开Chrome
somewhere nope
某处不
ok let's check out the API guide now
好的，让我们现在查看API指南
it's going to show this as an extra
这将显示为一个额外的
fields in the table automatically okay
表格中的字段会自动好吗
so here windows they're there and there
所以在这里窗户在那里
are basically a number they're not an
基本上是一个数字，他们不是
int because in Jason is the number okay
int因为在Jason中这个数字还可以
so you have a couple of Jason types
所以你有几种Jason类型
there yes
有
yes
是
that here can get out
可以离开这里
yeah but do you okay so the question is
是的，但是你还好吗，问题是
can we put this description out of the
我们可以把这个描述排除在外吗？
tests which makes a test more verbose
测试使测试更加冗长
and put that in the in the poggio as an
并把它作为一个
annotation there as a description
注释在那里作为描述
annotation for that field yeah I mean
该字段的注释是的，我的意思是
yeah that would be a valid approach
是的，这将是一种有效的方法
although it's it's basically just a
虽然它基本上只是一个
question of what do you want to where do
你想在哪里做什么的问题
you want to pollute code basically and I
你想基本上污染代码，我
would argue that the production code is
会认为生产代码是
already full of annotations and it's
已经充满注解了
already complex enough you probably
你已经足够复杂了
wouldn't want to put it there although I
我不想把它放在那里
mean it doesn't support it because it's
表示它不支持它，因为它
really it wants to get away from the
真的，它想摆脱
swagger approach where you put your
放荡的方法，你把你的
production code full of annotations so
生产代码充满注解，因此
it kind of tries not to do that
尝试不这样做
although I mean if you use swagger it's
虽然我的意思是如果你用招摇
probably the way to go there because
可能去那里的方式，因为
that's also in your project that you
那也在你的项目中
want to annotate stuff but then I mean
想注释东西，但是我的意思是
sometimes there are more annotations for
有时会有更多的注释
swagger than actual code of production
比实际生产规范大张旗鼓
code so it might be something you can
代码，所以可能是可以的
you might make an issue in the in the
您可能会在
github repo and see what Andy tell us
github仓库，看看安迪告诉我们什么
about that but I think this is kind of a
关于这个，但我认为这有点像
coherent way because it's a fluent API
连贯的方式，因为它是流利的API
as well so it actually it forms a nice
以及它实际上形成了一个很好的
hole in the integration test alright so
集成测试中的漏洞
if there are more questions definitely
如果肯定还有更多问题
come find me I'm going to be outside and
来找我，我要在外面，
walking around here so thanks for your
在这里走来走去，谢谢你
attention guys
注意人